近来
美国监狱系统面临着崩溃的边缘
私人集团接管了所有监狱
并以此牟利
而"围栏"集团则成为了
死亡岛监狱的新东家
《死亡飞车2》
嘿 你们他妈的搞定了吗?
Hey, are you gooks almost done?
死玻璃
Faggot.
你就是一混蛋 懂吗? 没错
You are big motherfucker, yes? Yeah.
就在刚才 死亡岛监狱爆发了全体大暴乱
Just moments ago, a full scale riot broke out at Terminal Island Penitentiary.
据我所知 目前 死亡岛内部官员
As far as I can tell, there has been no action taken
依然没有做出响应
by Terminal Island Prison correction officers.
封锁吊桥 加强守卫
Lock down the bridge, keep the tower guards.
让大家快点下来
I want everyone else down here now.
太爽了
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
我当然没有开玩笑啊你他妈快点过来直播!
Of course I'm serious! Patch me live right fucking now!
要不然我就向你老婆揭你老底
Either you take me live or I tell your wife everything.
别告诉我你没有拍到
You got that, right?
真他妈的扫兴
What a shit match.
如果我早知道斯皮罗受伤 就不会下注了
I would never have bet if I knew Spiro was injured.
但是你还是下注了 对吧 没错 让你赢了
But you did, huh? Yeah. Take your winnings.
曼联和这世道一样 都垮掉了
The whole world's falling apart, and Manchester United with it.
我刚出道的时候
When I came over here,
那夹子是我用所有的钱 买的第一件东西 知道吗?
that clip was the first thing I ever bought with my own money, you know?
所以 你要保管好 照看好它
So, you take care of it. You look after it.
瞧你 靠足球赚了那么多 可是却从来也没看过一场比赛
Look at you, profiting off football. He's never watched a match in his life.
那是因为比赛实在是无聊
That's 'cause it's fucking boring, that's why.
就因为这... 它可是世界第一大运动啊
The world's greatest game.
应该说是第三大吧 对吗?
I think it's the third world's greatest game, right?
你丫的笑什么?
What the fuck are you laughing at?
一边去 拜托
Excuse us, please.
银行那事儿
About the bank,
对我很重要
its important to me.
我知道的
I know it is.
所以我让我的人去处理
That's why I want to handle it my way, with my guys.
对了 维尼把比分告诉我了
Well, Vinnie brought me this score.
我的事就交给你了 你办事我放心
My stipulation is that you're in charge, which is the way I want it.
感觉靠谱吗? 你觉得呢?
Can I count on you? What do you think?
当然靠谱
Yeah.
我知道维尼和他手下还有点嫩
I know Vinnie and his boys are a bit green,
但是虽然我侄子缺少经验 热情却有的是
but what my nephew lacks in experience, he makes up for with enthusiasm.
我正是担心这一点
Exactly what I'm worried about.
可是他很操蛋 凯恩先生 他总是敷衍我
Look, he fucks up, Mr. Kane, he answers to me, okay?
没关系的 卢克 相信我
Lt's going to be all right, Luke. Trust me.
一直都很相信
Always do.
我知道
I know you do.
跟我来 让你看样东西
Come on. I've got something to show you.
意下如何?
What do you think?
给我的?
This is for me?
不喜欢? 没 挺漂亮的
You don't like it? I think it's beautiful.
我只是想 无功不受禄
I just think, maybe, you know, based on the kind of work I do,
而且你不觉得颜色有点太"橙"了
you don't think its a bit orange?
看来你不喜欢... 别开玩笑了
You don't fucking like it. Are you kidding me?
她简直太炫了
She's stunning.
我只是在想 你觉得我应该高调点吗?
I just wonder, you think I might stand out in this thing?
当然 你越高调 你就越不会被怀疑
No, the more obvious you are, the less suspicious you appear.
那就是说 咱们这是"灯下黑"
So, like, hiding in plain sight kind of thing.
完全正确
Precisely.
好的
Okay.
别搞砸了
Don't fuck it up.
谢谢各位赏脸
Thank you both for coming.
卫兰德先生 我真不知道她怎么在这儿
Mr. Weyland, I'm not exactly sure why she's here,
但是我来这儿是有原因的 我让您失望了 且让公司蒙辱
but I know why I am, sir. I've failed you and I've disgraced the corporation.
放松点
Relax.
我很奇怪他们怎么不杀人了
I'm surprised those animals don't kill each other with more regularity.
让你们来是因为这件事
You're both here because this incident has created
所引起的公众影响让我寝食难安
a public relations nightmare for me.
我说的难道是笑话吗?
Was something I said funny?
额 咱们的收视率才有4.8成
Well, you had a 48 share.
可是咱之前最高的时候是7成
Your network's previous high was a seven.
对于你说是噩梦 可是我却觉得是美梦
What you call a nightmare I'd call a wet dream.
卫兰德先生 我知道网络不是您的摇钱树
Mr. Weyland, I know that the network isn't your prime moneymaker.
但是我真不敢相信 您还没有意识到它其实就是一个金矿
But I can't believe that you don't realise what a gold mine you're sitting on.
愿闻其详 琼斯小姐
Humour me, Miss Jones.
人们厌倦了伪暴力
People are tired of fake violence
厌倦了维加斯那些托儿们
and fights staged by Vegas promoters.
可是那些囚犯内心充满了仇恨
The hatred that your inmates have
这种恨 是无法表演出来的
is pure. Can't be duplicated.
你们说今天的事是一场"秀"?
You're calling what happened today entertainment?
啊!
Ah!
你那脑袋里到底有什么鬼主意?
What exactly do you have in mind?
说真的 我要告诉你
No, seriously, I gotta tell you,
那家伙之前已经有20年没有摸枪了
this motherfuckers never carried a gun in 20 years working for my uncle.
就是这回事 卢克 维尼 用点儿心
That right, Luke? Vinnie, pay attention.
一分钟时间 全部搞定
You got 60 seconds. You get in, you get out.
不要动手 了解 放心吧
No one gets hurt. We know. Don't worry.
条子来了 快撤
We got company. Get out of there.
维尼 收到了吗?
Vinnie, you copy?
别担心 伙计 瞧你吓得
Don't worry about it, man. Don? stress 0ut.
听好 撤 快点
Look, abort. Get out of there. Chill, man.
淡定 伙计 小琼斯 撤了 撤 快点
Jonesy, abort. Abort. Get out of there.
由我掌控 操
It's under control. Fuck.
你他妈的给我趴下! 快他妈趴下!别你妈看我!
Get the fuck down! Get the fuck down! Don't look at me!
不许动!
Freeze!
不许动! 不许动!
Freeze! What the fuck?
嘿!
Hey!
真白痴!
Fucking idiot!
20年了我没有再伤人
Twenty years and nobody got hurt.
可是你 臭小子
You. Dumb fuck.
给我滚出去! 快!
We're leaving now! Move!
见鬼 操
Shit! Fuck!
妈的!混蛋! 快走 快走!
Shit! God damn it! Go, go, go, man!
快 我们撤了!
Come on, let's move!
真是扫兴!
Fuck this, then.
你看啥呢? 住手!
What are you looking at? Stop!
你这疯子!
You're crazy!
快走! 不许动!
Move! Freeze!
我们快点闪人吧!
Let's get the fuck out of here!
快 快 快 快 快!
Go. Go, go, go, go!
快上车 维尼
Get in the fucking car, Vinnie. Right.
快走! 要撤了!
Move! Gotta go!
你要干嘛?要干嘛?
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你想让我们去下面见泰瑞吗?
You're going to get us fucking killed, like Terry.
是你们害死泰瑞的 少废话了!
The only motherfucker that got Terry killed was you. Fucking relax!
瞧我给他们点颜色看看
We're gonna blast our way through.
你要给谁点颜色看看? 现在还搞不明白状况吗?
No one's getting blasted, you fucking understand me?
卢克 他们追上来了 想抓我没门!
They're gaining on us. Luke, fuck, I ain't getting pinched.
你干嘛? 你这是他妈要干嘛啊?
What the fuck are you doing? What the fuck are you doing?
为什么要非要那样做?
What the fuck was that for?
你妈的 放下枪
Fuck you. Drop the fucking gun.
自己选吧 操
Make a choice. Fuck.
你叔叔是我的恩人
Your uncle is family.
所以你们才能全身而退 滚出去
It's the only fucking reason you guys are walking from this. Get out.
快给我出去!
Get out the fucking car!
《快乐主厨》第一季又回来了
Chefs from Season 1 are back for redemption,
...好似好戏还没有真正开始...
...and it appears there's even more...
...银行抢劫嫌疑人被抓了个正着...
...bank robbery suspect is caught red handed...
还需要进一步确认 恐怕 荣恩
Wall that's still yet to be confirmed I'm afraid, Ron,
目前 繁忙的国王大道 正在渐渐的恢复以往的平静
as busy King Street is starting to get back to normal right now.
就在几个小时前 这里还上演着警匪火拼的好戏
Just a few hours ago, it was the scene of high tension as gunfire rang...
四名嫌犯中 有一位的身份已经得到确认
Of the four suspects, one has been identified
他的名字是卡尔·卢卡斯 据可靠信息来源称
as Carl Lucas, who is a known associate
他受雇于马库斯·凯恩
of alleged crime boss Markus Kane. Fuck!
现在我们正在现场为您直播... 去死吧!
We will now take you live downtown... Fucking hell!
站在原地不许动!
Stay where you are!
举起手来
Hands up!
(六个月后)
最后看一眼老家吧 老小子们
Take a last look at the mainland, boys.
要过桥了 看一眼少一眼了
You ain't gonna see her again once we cross this bridge.
说起来桥 庞恰特雷恩湖大桥是最长者之一
Bridges. Lake Pontchartrain Causeway is the longest,
总长达38.5公里
38 and a half kilometres long,
而第二大桥 东海大桥 总长达32.5公里
followed by Donghai Bridge, 32 and a half kilometres long.
法赫德国王大桥排第三 满口胡言 说起没完的小杂种
The King Fahd Causeway comes in third. Fucking mumbling, stuttering bastard.
你他妈的可以闭嘴吗? 关你什么事?
Could you shut the fuck up'? Leave him alone.
10分钟犯一次叨叨病
Prattling on every 10 minutes.
你他妈的都不觉得烦? 他只不过是吓坏了而已
I'm getting sick and fucking tired of you. He's scared.
那有你什么事呢?
What do you care?
没有我事
I don't.
好了 动起来
All right! Let's move!
都出来 出来
Get out! Get out!
动作快点 别磨蹭 都下车 快下去
Move! Come on, move! Get out here! Get out here!
别你妈动我!
Get the fuck off me.
快 都跟上 跟上
Come on, get out. Come on now.
我绝对不会指证 绝不会
l will not testify Never.
DA会考虑为你减刑 卢克
The DA's gonna pull his offer Luke.
如果凯恩没事的话 你也能大摇大摆地走出去
Kane'll walk away scat free, and you'll go away for life.
告诉你了 我不会指正马库斯·凯恩的
You see, I'm not gonna testify against Markus Kane.
既不为名 也不会为了利
Not for immunity not for money
什么也不为
not for anything.
有好消息要告诉你 凯恩先生 我们找到卢克了
We have some good news, Mr. Kane. We found Luke.
他就在岛上 确实是好消息
He's on the Island. That is good news.
就知道他值得信任
Always knew I could trust that guy.
告诉过你们 他不会出卖我们的
I told you. No way would he betray me.
得把他弄出来
Have him taken out.
你在说笑呢吧?
You're joking, right?
目前 他还没有和条子合作
So far, he hasn't played ball with the feds.
可是他判的是终身监禁 谁知道以后会不会 你说对吧?
He's in for life. What happens after a month of hard time, eh?
万一他们对他刑讯逼供了怎么办?
After a couple of them African apes have a go at him.
你觉得在那种情况下他能撑多久?
How long do you think he's gonna slay loyal then?
说实话 真是憾事一件啊
You know, it's a shame,
因为我待他就像是自己的兄弟一般
'cause I love that guy like a brother.
还有别的事吗?
Anything else?
没了 先生
No, sir.
你觉得怎么样呢? 挺完美的
What else do you wanton this? It's perfect.
是吗 给 谢谢
Yeah? Here, then. Thank you.
去死吧!
Fuck you!
每场比赛的收视率在5成左右
The average Death Match fight gamers a 50 share.
两个月之前飙到了6.2成 但是之后一路下滑
It peaked two months ago at 62, but has been on the decline since.
这儿最厉害的打手是比格·比尔 已经让19人命丧黄泉
The most dangerous fighter is Big Bill, with a death count of 19,
然后就是 14K
followed by 14K,
他也杀了14个了 不错 伙计
who, coincidentally, has 14 kills. Great, man.
看来你知道的蛮多的嘛
Someone did their homework, right'?
是他吗? 没错
Is that him? Yeah.
她叫琼斯 前世界小姐
That's September Jones. Former Miss Universe.
她靠的是《一脱到底》博得了5为评审的一致青睐
Was stripped of her crown after allegations of a sexual relationship with all five judges.
后来进入维兰德电视台做了天气预报员
Went to work for Weyland Broadcasting as a weather girl,
而现在却当上了《你死我活》的制片人
is now the host and executive producer of Death Match,
她...
She grew a...
你小子...是不是什么都想尝试下啊我没说错吧?
You have a list pretty much ready to go on anything, don't you?
"死亡岛"的现场直播 史上最令人不寒而栗 问而生畏
Live from Terminal Island televisions most violent most disturbing,
但又欲罢不能的电视节目
and most watched programme in human history.
欢迎大家收看
Welcome to Death Match.
我们第一位参赛者 被判四次终身监禁
Our first fighter a murderer serving four consecutive life sentences,
山德·格雷迪!
Xander Grady!
山德身负11条人命 终身监禁
Xander 11 kills, one submission.
6尺4寸，220磅
6'4" 220 pounds.
他的对手是"死亡终结3人组"的老大
His opponent leader of the Terminal Island Triads,
目前位于排行榜第二名
he currently ranks second on the kill board
当年是国际刑警租狙击榜上头三甲 直到去年才在洛杉矶落入法网
he was Interpol's third most wanted until his arrest in Los Angeles last year:
14K 身负14条人命 终身监禁
14K one submission, 14 kills.
5尺11寸，159磅
5'11" 159 pounds.
每周的比赛人选通过抽签产生
The combatants are picked by lottery randomly each week.
要赢有两种方式 杀了他 或者逼他就范
There are two ways to win. Kill your opponent or make him submit.
下面的感压阀 一旦被激活
There are several pressure plates that, when activated
与赛者便可有机会得到各种武器
can give a fighter access to a variety of weapons.
但武器必须要在10秒内获得
But they only have 10 seconds to access them.
如果没人胜出 那么庄家通杀
If no fighter has won, both fighters are killed.
各位观众 好戏即将登场
Dim the lights. The carnage is about to begin.
你才是第一美姐儿!
You're number one!
第一美姐儿!
Number one!
哟 宝贝 你就是我们的第一美姐嘿!
Yo, baby, you're my number one!
小混蛋!
Chinese bastard!
有点不对劲
Something's not right.
怎么个情况?
What're you talking about?
去死吧!
Die!
你就那么想死吗?哼?
You want it? Huh?
去死吧 伙计!
Let go, man!
我是不会投降的!
I will never give up!
他降了! 才不是!
He quit! No!
又是一次降!
Another fucking submission!
他投降了
He quit!
《你死我活》是维兰德国际娱乐旗下的一档栏目
Death Match is a trademark of Weyland International.
与赛者全是亡命之徒 警告观众请勿模仿
Fighters are convicted violent felons. Acts should not be duplicated at home.
你知道自己在做什么吗?
Exactly what the fuck do you think you are doing?
你死定了!
You are done.
死定了!
Done!
关灯!
Lights out!
嘿 甜心儿
Hey, baby.
今晚的数据进来了
The numbers from the overnights are in.
知道我请你来不是吃干饭的吗?
What do I pay you for?
收视率又跌了 这次只有两成
The ratings are down again. This time, 20%.
你最后能挽救颓势 否则我就另请高明
Now, you better reverse the trend, or I'll End someone who can.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
对 我确定 你现在拿着我的钱 懂了吗?
Yes, I'm sure. Now, you make my motherfucking money. You understand me?
"死亡三人组"很铁
It's a strict Triad code.
不论是谁惹了他们 那他就泥菩萨过江 自身难保了
Whoever spills the blood of a Triad, they're sworn to take that person's life.
山德在上次比赛中杀了其中之一
Xander killed a Triad last match.
其实这就有点不符合常理 刚才那么好的机会 他却没有抓住
It defies logic why he wouldn't kill him if he had the chance.
嘿 小子 我可不是来找朋友来了 懂吗?
Hey, kid, I'm not looking for a best friend, okay?
所以说 请别烦我了
So, just leave me alone.
卡尔·卢卡斯
Carl Lucas.
淡定 淡定 伙计 放松点
Chill. Chill, man. Relax.
你被分到我们工作组了
You've been assigned to our work detail.
这是拉库
That's Rocco,
我叫 金伯格
I'm Goldberg.
金伯格 哈?
Goldberg, huh? Yeah.
没错 莫非你就是传说中... 那最后一个墨西哥犹太人 还是谁?
What are you, like, then. You, like, the last Mexican Jew, or what?
嗯 我把其他人都宰了
Yeah. I killed all the rest.
好吧 说到工作 我们负责什么呢?
Okay. So, this work detail, what are we looking at?
别告诉我咱们是洗内裤的
And don't tell me we're washing underwear.
我不管你喜欢做什么
No. I don't care what you're into.
我才不是盥洗工
I'm not washing anybody's underwear.
跟我来 卢卡斯 华登找你说话
On your fest, Lucas. Warden wants you.
没你们的事了
That'll be all.
卡尔·卢卡斯 20年内 被捕22次
Carl Lucas, arrested 22 times over a span of 20 years.
但是没有什么大过 一个也没有
But nothing ever stuck, not a single damn one.
你总是能逢凶化吉
You just slipped through the cracks.
额 这次我杀了条子
Well, I shot a cop.
可是人无千日好 花无百日红
Those cracks, they till up pretty fast.
是这么个理
They sure do. Yeah.
起初我没有意识到你到底是何方神圣
Now, at first I didn't realise who you were.
真的吗? 那现在呢?
Really? So, who am I'?
额 白痴一个 很快就入土了
Well, an idiot, and soon a dead man.
国际刑警让你出庭作证 你把他们拒了?
DA offers you a talk and walk, and you tum him down?
就为这事让我来?
Is that why you gut me here?
不 不全是 我是想警告你
No, ifs not. I'm here to warn you.
省省吧 别自以为是
Save your breath. Oh, don't get smart with me.
我不知道别人是怎么听说你的
I don't know how many others know who you are,
但是有口风放出来
but when the word gets out,
有杀手要取你小命
the killers are gonna be coming out of the woodwork.
真是这事?
Is that right?
记住我的话
And mark my words,
马库斯·凯恩不会像你待他 那样待你的
Markus Kane will not show you the same type of loyalty that you've shown him.
听着 如果14K杀了山德
Look, 14K kills Xander,
他会被认为是殉道者 十分风光
he makes him a martyr. Thais like an honour.
但是投降 则意味着他们几个蒙受了奇耻大辱
Xander quits, shames himself and the entire brotherhood.
让别人觉得他是胆小鬼
That makes him like a pussy.
你们带他来了 伙计们?
You got him, guys?
没错
Yeah.
哦 老天
Oh, man.
我有个问题 鼓捣这些个汽车 应该不是咱们该干的事吧
I got a question. All these cars, man, it's not exactly prison norm.
到底是怎么一档子事?
What's the deal?
嘿 "死亡岛"才不是什么感化院 很明显吧
Hey, Terminal Island is not about rehabilitation. You know what I mean?
其实早就产业化了 这些汽车 我们熔化了他们
It's a business. All these cars, we melt them down,
然后用于生产枪支 弹药
make weapons, guns, shells.
制造一切可以用来杀人的玩意
If it kills, we make it.
嘿 你是说... 政府资助的钱 全用来回收破烂了?
Hey, are you telling me the governments paying top dollar for this recycled shit?
政府投资? 哪个说政府投资了?
Top dollar? Who said anything about top dollar?
维兰德国际把这些东西都贱卖了
Weyland International sells this stuff dirt cheap.
当然了 咱们又不用付钱的
Yeah, when you're not paying for labour,
这样价钱当然就很低了 知道怎么一回事了吧?
your prices can afford to be a little lower, you know what I mean?
他们在榨我们的血!
They're making money off our blood.
对车懂吗? 一点点
What do you know about these wheels? A little bit.
它状况怎么样? 自己体验下吧?
How does she run? Why don't you see what she's got?
当真? 当真
For real?? For real.
何乐不为呢?
Why not?
有人要开车越语咯!
Someone's been driving a getaway car!
老天啊你还真有两把刷子
God damn, you put some magic in this thing.
它状况如何? 应该没什么问题
How does she handle? Just the way she's supposed to.
谁刚才开车来着?
Who was driving that car?
什么车?
What car? What car?
嘿 卢克 你也要参赛?
Hey, Luke, you a fighter?
我为什么要参赛啊?
I got no reason to fight anyone.
嘿 参赛还要理由吗?
Hey, reasons don't mean shit in this place.
卡琳达正准备"提拔"新人呢
The Calendar's always looking for new blood,
你还真符合她的口味儿
and you look like just her type.
鬼才知道
Good to know.
给你点儿忠告 低调 别给她任何机会
Some advice, blend in. Don't give her no reason to fixate on you.
嘿 金伯格 我打死也不会去趟那浑水的
Hey, Goldberg, I'm the last guy looking for a fucking spotlight.
退后! 退后!
Stay back! Stay back!
大家都退后!
Everybody else stay back!
大家都不要过来 退后
I don't want you in there. Move back.
你们全部的人 都退后! 快! 退后!
All of you, stay back! Let's go! Move back!
什么情况? 大个自己摔了一跤
What's going on here? Big guy tripped.
是这么一回事 比尔? 嗯 我自己摔了
Thai so, Bill? Yeah, I tripped.
我没说错吧
That's what he says.
好了 继续 走吧
All right, let's go! Keep it moving!
快走! 动! 走!
Come on, move! Get moving! Move! Move!
那小家伙是谁啊?
Who's the little guy'?
- 他叫"百事通" - "百事通"?
- His name's "Lists". - "Lists"?
你没问题的
You'll work it out.
你连电脑都没有听过? 看来你已经out几千年了
You ever hear of a computer? You're, like, a century behind everyone.
可是我也奇怪为什么没有算盘...
I'm surprised I don't find an abacus in here.
有何贵干啊? 我来找他的
What are you doing in my office? I'm here for him.
卡尔·卢卡斯 光听名字就够给力的了
Carl Lucas. Even the name gives me a hard on.
连法官都称他为"怪兽" 他太完美了
The judge called him a monster at his trial. He's perfect.
我可以用他 没有那事
l can sell him. You can't have him.
我又不是来征求你同意的 等下 我还要交代下
I wasn't asking your permission. Wait. There's more to it.
国际刑警觉得这是一次机会
DA thinks there's a chance
可以让他出面指证马库斯·凯恩
that he could turn state witness against Markus Kane.
现在 你却想让他上你那节目?!
Now, you put him on your TV show,
别说那些人兽不如的家伙会宰了他
not only could those animals kill him,
就说 他的作用可以警示凯恩 让他知道还有一个污点证人活着
but basically, he just advertises to Kane where the chief witness against him sleeps,
然后他就会寝食难安了
and then he's a dead man.
那是卢卡斯先生的问题 跟我无关
Mr. Lucas' problem, not mine.
华登·帕克斯 你和你的监狱没有夸都是因为...
Warden Parks, you and your prison exist for one reason,
有《你死我活》这档节目
to facilitate Death Match.
可是我觉得咱们应该是 惩罚罪犯以保护咱们的社会秩序
And here I thought we were here to protect society and punish criminals.
那么你确实比我想的还要傻
Then you're dumber than I thought.
你们先回避一下
Give us a minute.
要毛巾吗
Would you like a towel?
不用了
I'm time.
嗯 好吧
Yeah, I'll say.
很给力啊
Very impressive.
昨天你和比格·比尔打了一架
And your fight with Big Bill yesterday,
也够给力的
also impressive.
我知道咱们以前没有见过... 我知道你是谁
I don't think we've met. I'm... Yeah, I know who you are.
救世主 对吗?
Save the sales pitch, huh?
我不会参赛的
I'm not fighting.
如果我想你参赛 你必须参赛
If I want you to tight, you fight.
是这么个事? 没错
Is that right? Yes.
虽然我不能改了你的判决
I can't do anything about the life sentences,
但是只要你参赛
but you participate,
我会让你在这儿的生活如天堂般
and I will make your life here much more tolerable.
单间 不用工作
Your own cell, no work detail,
上等食物
real food,
当然还有很多...
as well as plenty of
其它特权 好
perks. Okay.
那么说... 我...
So, I...
我帮你们赢几场比赛
I win some tights for you,
你就会再让别人取代我的位子
you need another guy to beat me.
我觉得 这有点...
I mean, that's...
太那个了 不觉得吗?
That's how it works, right?
没错
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
嘿
Hey,
去别人那儿卖笑吧
go sell sleazy someplace else,
因为我不买你的帐
'cause I ain't buying.
你别逼我 随你便吧
You won't leave me any choice. Do what you gotta do.
我才不上你的圈套呢
I'm not gonna be a part of your freak show.
我们走着瞧
We'll see.
嘿
Hey.
很少有人拒绝你吧
You don't hear the word "no" so often, do you?
只有我拒绝别人的份儿
Only when I say it.
各位观众 好戏即将上演
Dim the lights, the carnage is about to begin.
各位观众 晚上好 欢迎收看《你死我活》
Good evening, and welcome to Death Match.
我们将现场随机挑选两位选手 一切请您来见证
Two men will be randomly selected live, right before your eyes.
只有优胜者才能或者出去
Only the winner walks out alive.
今晚谁会是我们的战士呢?
Are there any fighters in here tonight?
还需要一位英勇的战士
I need one more.
不! 不!
No! No!
真是他妈的没天理
This is fucking bullshit.
欢迎收看 《你死我活》 栏目
Welcome to Death Match.
嘿! 嘿 好了 你的话我懂了
Hey! Hey, lady. Okay, you made your point.
把我换上去 噢 现在你又想打了?
Switch us up. Oh, so now you wanna fight?
你丫说对了 他们会要了他的命的 你心知肚明
Fucking right. They're gonna kill him in there, you know that.
当然 我当然希望如此了 因为咱们节目叫 《你死我活》嘛
Yeah, I certainly hope so. The name of the game is Death Match.
你他妈有什么毛病啊?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
嘿! 别碰我...
Hey! Get your fucking hands...
赢得比赛有两种方式 宰了你的对手 或者让他就范
There are two ways to win. Kill your opponent or make him submit.
这几枚感压碟 一旦激活
There are several pressure plates that, when activated
与赛者可以有机会得到各种武器
can give a fighter access to a variety of weapons.
然而本周 我们的新武器将会让你眼前一亮!
And this week we have a new weapon that will blow your mind.
加油!
Come on!
弄死他 比尔
Fuck him up, Bill!
快! 过来啊!
Come on! Come on!
我的个...
Mother...
那家伙疯了吧!
Motherfucker's crazy!
但是真帅啊!
But cool.
你这是要干嘛啊? 我想搏上一搏 你能帮忙吗?
What the fuck are you doing? I want on the floor. Can you help?
弄死他 卢克!
Get him, Luke!
小心!
Watch out!
小心啊!
你他妈给我过来! 来啊!
Get the fuck out of here! Go!
看来咱们的人有点不妙啊
Don't look good for our boy.
这边走! 这边! 快啊!
This way! This way! Come on!
门开了 卢克! 门!
The door, Luke! The door!
这算他妈的什么事啊! 这算是比赛吗还?!
This is some bullshit! This game is rigged!
烧死那白种驴! 那白种驴耍赖啊!
Barbecue his white ass! Yo, the white boy's cheating!
傻逼才他妈耍赖! 去你妈的 死老黑!
Fucking cracker's cheating! Fuck you, you nigger!
去死吧 你丫的!
You piece of shit! Watch out!
放马过来啊!
Come on!
快 我们也进去
Come on! Let's gel in there!
快 快 上 上 都过去!
Come on, come on! Go, go! Get out there!
早就说嘛
I told you.
糟了!
Switch!
快 快
Go, go, go!
跟我过来! 快 快!
Get the fuck over here! Come on! Come on!
回来
Get back.
小心点 卢克!
Watch out, Luke!
准备尖叫吧 臭婊子
Get ready to scream, bitch!
现在谁尖叫啊贱人!
Fuck you! Who's screaming now, bitch?
红色警戒 清场
Code red, arena stage.
停止转播 你他丫的疯了吗?
End transmission now. Are you fucking crazy?
快停止 没门 这是我的秀
Shut it down. No way. This is my show.
这是老子的地盘 快给我停止转播
And this is my prison. End this broadcast now
要不然把你也关进去 省得你觉得坐着闷得慌
or you're gonna be one of the cons instead of just filming them.
了解
Got it.
《你死我活》是维兰德国际娱乐旗下的一档栏目
Death Match is a trademark of Wayland International.
与赛者全是亡命之徒 警告观众请勿模仿
Fighters are convicted violent felons. Acts should not be duplicated at home.
爬在地上!
Get on the ground!
卢克!
Luke!
快 快上车
Come on, get on the bus!
想活吗? 给我趴着别动
You wanna live'? Stay down.
那不是卢克吗?
Wasn't that Luke?
什么?
What?
妈的!
Fuck!
给我电话!
Get me the phone!
妈的!
Fuck.
放松 好吗? 放松 不会痛的 放松
Just relax, huh? Just relax. Won't hurt a bit. Relax.
如果再近点儿... 老兄...
Any closer, buddy...
你还真是走运啊还好没有伤到股动脉
You're really lucky, or this would have hit the femoral artery.
嗯 没错 我总是很幸运 嗯 确实如此
Yeah, that's me. Lucky. Yeah. You can say that.
老天啊! 放松 放松
Man! Just relax. Relax.
出了点小问题 几个犯人翘辫子了
It's a minor setback. A few rapists and murderers died. Boo hoo.
算了吧 就这样了
No. This is the end.
是你一手搞砸的 所以才搞到现在这个局面
You messed it up by pulling the plug. We would've won the night.
别以为会脱就能左右逢源!
You're not good enough in bed to win this one.
回去做梦吧
Sweet dreams.
撑下 过去那边
Come on, over here.
妈的
Fuck.
坐下 闭嘴
Sit down there and shut up.
收声 嘿
Quiet down. Hey.
怎么了?
What happened?
记住能打的不止是你一个
You're not the only one that got in some good shots.
收到 好了 女士们 排好队
I know. All right, ladies! Line it up!
车要开了 别逼我吼第二次!
The bus is leaving. Don't make me tell you twice!
嘿 跟我走
Hey. Let's go.
谢你了
Thanks, huh? Step through, ladies!
嗯 我也不知道为什么那样做
Yeah. I don't know why I did it.
可能他们为此扔我进笼子里
Probably get thrown in the hole for that.
为什么?
Then why?
那你为什么帮那犯人呢?
Why did you help that con?
我不想让他替我而战
Wasn't gonna let the man fight my fight.
跟我来 快走
Right this way. Let's go.
你有名字吗?
You gut a name?
额 当然了 我有名字啊
Uh huh. Yeah. Of course I do.
走了 哥们
Come on, man.
他在那儿
There he is.
他怎么还活着呢?
How the fuck is he still alive?
老板 他们保证下次不会失手了
JOEY; Boss, we've been assured it's happening.
都快保证了一个月了
It's been happening for weeks now.
你以为他会继续沉默多久?
How much longer do you think he's gonna stay silent?
他是纯爷们 而且一直都很中心...
He's a tough guy, and he's been loyal...
我要他死!
I want him dead!
我们已经安插自己人了 十足的疯子
We have someone on the inside, a total psycho.
用不了多久了 乔伊 乔伊
It won't take long now..Joey. Joey.
盒子 它有棱有角
The box, with its implications of rigidity and squareness,
象征着对想象力的禁锢以及无尽的苦痛折磨
symbolises unimaginative thinking and painful frustration.
有时我们只需后退一步
Sometimes we just have to step back
站到盒子之外来看待整个问题
see if the solutions to our problem lies outside the box.
召集开会
Calla meeting.
都叫谁来? 所有人!
With who? Everyone!
你干嘛不回我电话啊? 很多人的电话我都不回
You didn't return my calls. I don't return a lot of calls.
我想讨论下《你死我活》 是时候重新启动了
I wanna discuss Death Match. I think that we should pull the plug.
你以为这是闹着玩呢? 说重启就重启?
When a real life not doesn't generate a second hour boost,
要我说咱们还是开源节流吧 没错 我们是改改进了
I'd say it's time to cut your loss. Exactly. We need to evolve.
我们得巩固我们的战果 而且我们也有豪华的主持阵容...
We've developed a strong base, we have legitimate TV stars...
琼斯小姐 董事会的决定谁也改不了
The board's decision is final, Miss Jones.
过去的半年里 只有我在为公司盈利
In the past six months, I'm the only profitable thing about this company.
除非你想我告你性骚扰 让你官司缠身
Unless you want a sexual harassment suit crammed down your throat,
这样你才能听进我说的话
you will listen to what I have to say.
好吧
Fine.
明早9点
9:00 a.m. tomorrow.
我有麻烦了
I'm troubled.
原本十分简单的任务 完成起来却依然曲曲折折
What seemed to be a very simple task has taken the most perplexing of turns.
所以这次我要讲得清楚
So I'm gonna speak slowly,
慢慢悠悠地
clearly,
省得你们漏听 或者误解
so my message is not lost, or ignored, or misinterpreted.
谁杀了卡尔·卢卡斯 100万美刀就是谁的
One million dollars to the man who kills Carl Lucas.
48小时之后完不成的话
This offer expires in 48 hours, and if that happens,
我会把你们当作敌人
I will consider you all enemies,
到时候等着自己的脑袋搬家吧
and I will bring war on your fucking head.
懂了吗?
Understand?
死亡岛上我们投资的9成
Ninety percent of Terminal Island,
都是无利润回报的
your grand investment, is dead space.
只有《你死我活》让你们苟延残喘
Death Match merely stayed your execution.
如果你们想要高枕无忧 就要有不做不休的精神
If you wanna get a breath of fresh air, you need a bold initiative.
我提议搞场比赛
I propose 3 race.
不能流芳百世 但求遗臭万年
Wicked. Epic.
绝对是前无古人后无来者
Something like no one has ever seen before.
比赛用轨道环绕整个死亡岛
The track will run the length of Terminal Island
其中各种曲折就不用我多说了
along some of the narrowest and most harrowing paths
更是赛车界中少见的
that the racing world has to offer.
更给力的则是 我们所需要的一切 都在自己后院
The best part of it, everything that we need is right in our own backyard.
车辆我们自己来改装
We're gonna modify each vehicle,
加装上装甲挡板 防弹玻璃 以及防滚笼
adding reinforced steel plating, bulletproof glass, and roll cages
让车手们有机会以一决高低
to at least give the drivers a fighting chance.
我们不惜一切让其噱头十足
We'll take everything that made Death Match a hit,
将我们手头的一切资源整合于此
combine it with everything we have at our disposal.
比如?
Such as?
各种重型武器
Heavy fucking artillery.
每辆车上都尽量配置上最多的武器弹药
Every car will hold as many guns and as much ammunition as it can,
换句话说你想让犯人们全副武装
So, you're going to arm the prisoners.
我们已经做好了防护措施 以保证他们只能互射
Precautions will be made to make sure they can only shoot at people on the track.
9辆车 3天 2万发子弹
Nine cars, three days, 20,000 rounds of ammunition.
从格斗到车斗 确实是一个大跨步啊
Going from righting to racing, that's a big leap.
我们需要一个过渡 使得二者之间的衔接更加自然
We need a hook. Something that incorporates the two better.
听着 在节目中 没人会在乎比赛本身 规则随便定
Now, in a game show, no one cares about the game. The game's arbitrary.
观众关注的是惊险程度以及奖惩情况
People care about the risk and the money.
我们一直关注着比赛 而没有考虑后者
Now, we've been concentrating on the game, not the risk.
所以观众们觉得无聊
That's why our audience is bored.
我们好好考虑下彩头如何设置
Let's concentrate on the prize.
比金钱更给力的彩头
A prize more valuable than money.
好吧 你觉得应该怎么办呢?
Okay. What's more valuable than money?
命
Life
比钱更重要
is a more valuable prize than money.
我们和政府的合约中 我们自己管判决这块儿
In our deal with the state, we control sentencing.
换句话说他们的命在我们手中
That means we control their life.
如果车手赢得五场比赛 那么他就自由了
So if a prisoner wins five races, he gets his freedom.
不管是因为什么进来的 不管是抢劫 强奸 还是杀人了 随便
No matter what he's in for, robbery, rape, homicide, whatever,
他都会获得释放
he wins his freedom.
获得重生
He wins his life.
所以说生命
You have life,
自由
freedom.
停
Stop.
就叫"死亡飞车"
Death Race.
跟你讲 真是他娘的垃圾 罗科
You know what? That's fucking bullshit, Rocco.
你知道个p 伙计
Well, how do you know, man? Maybe ifs for real.
万一是真的呢 你开玩笑呢?
Are you kidding me?
你们觉得他们会放了这些杀人犯 还有强奸犯出去吗 你们信吗?
You think they're gonna let murderers and rapists out of this place, ever'?
嘿 卢克说得对
Hey, Luke's right.
话说回来 你丫根本就不会开车
And besides that, homes, you don't drive worth a shit.
你们几个去死吧 就会那我打岔
You know what? Fucking blow me.
真是他妈死玻璃
Fucking faggot.
这可能是我唯一能出去的机会了
That would be the only chance I have of getting out.
出去之后你会做什么啊百事通?
And what would you do, Lists, if you got out?
重新做人
Start over.
欢迎收看《死亡飞车》
Welcome to Death Race.
"死亡岛"监狱接下来的3天 将会举行一次"死亡飞车"大赛
Terminal Island Penitentiary hosts three days of the ultimate in auto carnage.
而第一场的比赛10分钟后就会上演
Day one of the race begins in 10 minutes,
令人惊喜的是 我们将不会插播广告
and will be brought to you without commercial interruption
您的安危是我们的一切
by Wayland International Your safety is our top priority.
准备好了吗 好戏开始
Get ready. The show's about to begin.
不要换台 精彩比赛马上开始!
Dim the lights. The carnage is about to begin.
欢迎收看《死亡飞车》第一集
Welcome to day one of Death Race.
一共18名十恶不赦的罪犯
Before you, 18 cons vie for their freedom.
想进入第二天的比赛就必须保证撑下今天的3圈
They must survive all three laps in order to proceed to day two.
他们首先要克服的是?
Their first challenge?
只有9辆车!
There are only nine cars.
没错 各位 只有9辆车!
That's right, gentlemen. Nine cars!
开始!
90;
这是他妈的太爽了!
This is what I'm talking about!
9辆!
Mine!
情况越来越令人心旷神怡了!
This just keeps getting better and better!
嘿 宝贝 少说废话 多办事!
Hey, baby. How about a bit v rodet?
哦 宝贝 就你了!
Oh, baby, yeah!
少他妈臭美了!
Don't think so!
干嘛不让他揍你一顿啊?
Why did you let that con beat you?
抓紧!
Shit! Hang on!
这是干嘛用的?
Fuck! Hey, why do I need this?
我来帮你弄下 好吧 好吧 这是谁在说话?
You mind helping me out with this? Yeah. Yeah. Who am I talking to'?
你的智囊团呗
To talk to your pit team. Pit team?
智囊团? 卢克 听到你的声音还不错啊
Luke! Good to have you, man.
这些按钮可以控制 枪 汽油弹 烟幕弹 还有凝固汽油弹...
So, you got your guns, your oil, your smoke, and your napalm here.
别老盯着我啊! 比赛开始了!
Get your eyes on the road. Let's race.
库克! 我金伯格
Luke! Goldberg.
对 墨西哥老犹太来救你小命了
Yeah. The Mexican Jew's here to save your bony white ass.
听好 宝剑和盾牌到第二圈才能启动
Now, swords and shields don't play until the second lap.
除了那保时捷 你的车是最快的
You've got the fastest car out there, except the Porsche.
不要正面冲突 小心后面 把你们弄成肉饼!
And don't go head to head with that Ram, or he'll have you for lunch.
他妈的!
Son of a bitch!
看来咱们的日子不好过了
Looks like we're already on the menu.
尝尝吧
Eat this.
爽不爽啊?
You feel me, baby?
哈哈 吓死你了吧 就这点本事啊小伙?
Now I got you, baby! ls that all you got, pretty boy?
小心右面的那辆车
Careful of the one on the right!
正好
Good to know.
真不错啊! 太好了!
Yeah! That's my man! Yes!
他在哪呢?哪呢? 左边呢
Where is he? Where is he? To the left.
山大·格雷迪
Xander Grady.
加油! 正在努力!
Come on! Get it going!
妈的! 非得弄死你不可!
Fucking Chinese bastard! I'll kill you!
妈的! 杂种!
Shit! Bastard!
去死吧你!
Motherfucker!
第一圈跑得不错 卢克 现在快点去激活 宝剑
That was a great lap, Luke, but now you need to get to a sword plate, and fast.
激活宝剑 盾牌 和死亡头颅
Activate swords, shields and death heads.
宝剑 感压阀已激活
Sword pressure plates activated.
盾牌感压阀 已激活
Shield pressure plates activated.
快去找一个宝剑感压阀 卢克 快去找一个 宝剑感压阀
You gotta find a sword, Luke. You gotta find a sword plate.
没错 就这样
That's right. Get back to work.
那有一个!
There's one!
看到了 快去激活 快!
I see it. Go for it. Go for it!
宝剑感压阀 已激活
Sword pressure plate activated.
感想如何啊哥们?
Yeah! How do you like that one, boy?
他想干嘛?
What the hell is he doing?
他丫的开枪了!
Oh, jeez! Guns! Guns!
让子弹飞 让子弹飞一会儿!
Eat my lead, boy! Eat my lead!
趴下! 快!
Get down! Now!
嘿 快离他远点! 趴下!
Hey, get out of there! Get down!
感觉如何啊小伙?
How's it feel, boy?
快 该拐弯了
You gotta turn here!
马上就拐
I'm working on it.
抓紧啊
Hang on.
老天啊! 哦 不!
God! Oh, God, no!
好!
Yeah!
呜 耶! 真他妈险啊
Ooh, yeah! That was close.
押注赛车是在禁酒时期开始流行的
Stock car racing got its start during Prohibition
比赛的都是些酒鬼联邦特工
with moonshine runners fleeing federal agents.
1947年比尔·法兰西在佛罗里达的代托纳 提议举办"全国运动汽车竞赛协会"
Bill France Sr. conceived NASCAR in 1947 during a meeting in Daytona, Florida.
"百事通" 我了解了!
"Lists." I get it now.
盾牌感压阀 已激活
Shield pressure plates activated.
混蛋
Motherfucker.
给来个特写 二号摄像师 往左边点
Get a close up on that. Camera two, move to your left.
他去哪了? 昂?
Where did he go? Huh?
哪去了他?
Where did he go?
想跑 没门!
You ain't escaping me now.
百万美刀 是我的啦!
A million dollars. It's gonna be mine.
他说什么?
What did he just say?
回放给我听
Replay that for me.
百万美刀 是我的啦!
A million dollars. Its gonna be mine.
我来处理
I'll take care of it.
你来开
Take the wheel.
给你点颜色看看 觉得自己很了不起?
Take that, bitch. Think you're special?
不!
No!
不要! 不!
No! No!
不!
No!
最后一圈了 卢克 马上就完了
One lap to go, Luke. This is it.
放松点 宝贝 放松
Stay with me, baby. Stay with me.
哦 耶!
Oh, yeah!
爽!
Yeah!
畜生! 躲开点儿! 躲开点!
Damn it! Get out of there! Get out of there!
真他妈受够了!
Enough of this shit.
什么情况? 抓紧
What the hell? Hang on.
淡定 淡定
Stay with me. Stay with me.
他发的哪门子的疯? 我怎么知道
What's he doing? I don't know.
太好了! 真不错! 真厉害啊!
Yeah! All right! All right!
真他妈的 混蛋!
Bullshit, motherfucker!
对 就这样
That's it. That's it.
宝剑感压阀 已激活
Sword pressure plate activated.
不对!
Not that one!
你傻啊干嘛把后挡板丢了?
Did you just drop our fucking tombstone?
额 我的错
Yeah, my bad.
大事不妙
Not good.
你干嘛?
What you doing?
你要干嘛? 好好开你的车 帅哥
What you doing? Drive, pretty boy.
"帅哥"
"Pretty boy."
他妈的这破车!
God damn this fucking car!
抓紧啊!
Hang on!
给你点颜色看看 混蛋!
Take this, you asshole!
去死吧
Eat that! Fuck!
抓紧 去死吧你!
Hang on! You're going down!
真是不错啊
That's nice work.
少废话!
Talk to me!
现在你死定了吧!
Now you're going down!
漂亮
Sweet!
有你真是我的福啊!
I guess I lucked out, then.
厉害
Nice.
刚才我们表现得神吧 金伯格
Guess we put that magic to work Goldberg. Well, brave!
加油 卢克 漂亮!
Come on, Luke! Yeah!
"死亡飞车"首战初捷!
The debut of Death Race is in the books.
卡尔·卢卡斯 是当之无愧的黑马
Carl Lucas is the surprise winner
后面的排名依次是比格·比尔 卡林 阿帕奇 山德 还有14K
followed by Big Bill, Calin, Apache, Xander and 14K.
卡尔·卢卡斯能撑到最后吗?
Can Carl Lucas hold on to win his freedom?
敬请各位关注明天的比赛
Tune in tomorrow to find out.
耶! 耶!
Yeah! Yeah!
伙计 你开车还真是一流啊!
Man! You can drive, man! What a rush, old man.
嘿 金伯格 你搞笑呢?
Hey, Goldberg, you kidding me'?
嘿 你是从哪里学的那招啊?
Hey, where'd you learn that?
我可当过女童军的啊真的啊?
I was a Girl Scout. Really?
看我怎么教训你 妈的! 你没病吧?
I'm gonna get you, fucker! ls that right?
你他妈明天比赛的时候等着!
You don't mess with somebody in this motherfucking race!
你他妈吓唬谁呢?
Is that a fucking date? Yeah!
是吗 来啊臭小子!
Yaah? Come on! Fucking pretty boy! Gonna fucking blow up your ass!
来啊借你两个胆 婊子!
Come on, suck my dick, bitch!
嘿 百事通 去跟他过两招 去啊
Hey, Lists, go kick his ass. Come on.
明天你死定了
Tomorrow, you die.
你的口臭死了
卡特里娜 该走了
Katrina! Let's go.
嘿 我明天能再见到你吗? 看你够不够走运咯
Hey, so I get to see you tomorrow, or what? If you're lucky.
妈的
Damn.
嘿 走吧 去小睡一会儿 哥们们
Hey, come on, snap out of it, guys.
嘿 百事通 你好好修理下它
Hey, Lists, you gotta fix it up there under here.
这儿 还有这儿
Right here. Right in here.
快 卢卡斯 赶紧的
Come on, Lucas, let's go.
听见了吗 快走 嘿 干嘛抓我啊?
You heard him. Move. Hey, what did I do?
快睡觉!
Goto sleep!
嘿 真他妈扯淡!
Hey, this is bullshit!
干嘛拉我过来?
Okay, what did I do'?
因为你赢了
You won!
有功者当赏 有过者当罚
To the victor belongs the spoils.
好吧 你到底什么意思?
Okay, so what does that mean'?
什么情况?
What is this?
在古罗马 获得胜利的角斗士将会得到恩赐
In ancient Rome, the winning gladiator was the recipient of gifts.
当权者为了表示爱才
A show of gratitude from the powers that be
将会表示自己最大的诚意
for a job well done.
她是你的了
She's yours.
想怎么她就怎么样吧
Do with her what you please.
这样做对吗?
Is that right?
你以为你是哪根葱啊?
And who the fuck are you?
我是人间的主宰
I'm Caesar.
跟你讲 他们可能在偷看我们呢
You know, they're probably watching.
应该还在偷听吧
Listening, too, I guess.
他们把我们当猴耍了
Some kind of game they're playing.
额 可能在打赌咱们下面会做什么
Yeah, probably betting on what we'll do next.
首先 他们想让咱们走得更近
Option A, they're trying to get us closer
这样可以利用我们其中一个对付另一个
so they can use one of us against the other.
第二种可能性 是让我们互相生疑 然后在比赛的时候失利?
Option B being, maybe, put a wedge between us, so we fuck up on the track?
那就随他们的意吧
I guess we do what they want,
随他们想怎么样
and leave the bullshit for later.
你在开我玩笑吗?
You playing me?
那又怎么样呢?
Does it matter?
没有
No.
凯恩出价一百万要卢卡斯的命
Kane put a million dollar bounty on Lucas,
所有人都盯着奖金呢
and all the bangers are going for it.
先把卢卡斯先生单独关起来
Put Mr. Lucas in solitary.
虽然我觉得咱们自己可以解决 不过这事太大了 保安可能都会说漏嘴的
I thought this was a prison thing, but this is too big for even the guards to resist.
你还会让他比赛吗? 嗯 对
You still gonna let him race? Oh, yeah.
不过想杀他必须要知道有摄像机盯着你们呢
They're free to kill him on the track, just not off camera.
那他怎么办?
What about him?
等下 等下
Wait! Wait!
快 跟我们走
Come on. Let's go.
你们爽过了 快走
You had your fun. Move.
咱们这是去哪啊? 闭嘴
Where are we going? Shut up.
这是他妈什么情况?
What the fuck is this?
卡特里娜 这儿的视野真是开阔啊
Beautiful view of freedom from here, Katrina.
好吧
Okay.
但是你是谁呢?
But who are you?
你本人还真是个可人儿啊
You're much more attractive in person.
过奖啊你想怎么样呢?
I'm flattered. What do you want?
卡尔·卢卡斯 我想要他的命
Carl Lucas. I want him dead.
作为回报 我给你自由
And in return, I offer you freedom.
给你一次重新做人的机会
A chance of life outside these walls
完成一个简单任务
for one simple task.
你只有48小时 你杀了他要么我杀了你
You've got 48 hours. You kill him or I kill you.
请抓住这次获得自由的机会
Let me make these walls disappear.
想象下自己在外面世界的样子 卡特里娜
Let me make you part of the view from outside, Katrina.
自由啊
Freedom.
48小时
Forty eight hours.
任务开始
Tick tuck.
喂? 65成的收视率啊
Yeah? Sixty Eve share.
做得好 小姑娘
Well done, young lady.
这已经是最好的了
It's truly for the best.
你不高兴 董事会也不高兴
You weren't happy, the board wasn't happy.
我们需要一个志同道合的人管理这里
We need someone for this institution that shares the common vision.
但不是你
Just wasn't you.
Park狱长 我们送你出去
Warden Parks, we're hereto escort you from the premises.
挖陷者 必自坠也
"whosoever diggeth a pit shall fall therein."
旧约 箴言 26段27章
Proverb 26:27.
那陷阱很深吗
Is that supposed to be deep?
希望你掉下去的时候 很深
Hopefully deep enough that, when you fall,
到时候你他妈的就可以摔断脖子了
you'll break your fucking neck.
你想怎么样 该比赛了
What do you want? Time to race.
你他妈的最好小心点 Luke
You got a big fucking bulls eye on your back Luke.
你觉得陷入重围了吗
You feel all those eyes on you?
不是因为你长得帅 也不是你得了第一
Ain't 'cause you're pretty or because you're in first place.
Markus Kane出一百万美元买你的人头
Markus Kane put a million dollars on your head.
这可是他妈的一大笔钱 Lucas
It's a monster fucking bounty, Lucas.
大家都知道了
It's as plain as day.
我才不信
I don't believe it.
我干嘛要撒谎
Why would I lie?
这对我来说毫无意义
It makes no fucking sense.
你准备怎么办
What're you gonna do?
二 一 开始了
Two, one, and we're in.
欢迎观看死亡飞车
Welcome to Death Race.
开始的18位参赛者 现在只剩下了6个
Eighteen men started. Only six remain.
估计昨天有五千万观众见证了Lucas的胜利
An estimated 50 million people watched Carl Lucas win day one.
他能再次重现夺冠的一幕吗
Can he do it again?
其它的参赛者可不会让他轻易取胜
Five other racers will have something to say about that.
欢迎来到死亡比赛的第二个比赛日
Welcome to day two of Death Race.
关上灯 好戏即将上演
Dim the lights. The carnage is about to begin.
嘿 你们今天早上爽了吗
Hey! Aren't you two just bubbling over with sunshine this morning?
加油 赢下这场比赛
Come on. We got a race to win.
怎么了
What is it?
没什么
Nothing.
那开始比赛吧
Let's race.
我抓到你了 混蛋
I've got you now, motherfucker!
注意后面
Coming up behind you!
小心
Watch out!
耶 被爆菊了吧
Yeah! I just fucked your ass!
把武器灯给他点亮
Activate swords and shields.
武器系统启动 操
Sword plate activated. Damn!
小心你后面 注意
Watch your back! Careful.
枪来了
Here comes the guns.
你要找个防具灯 伙计
You gotta End a shield, man.
快找个防具灯
You gotta find a shield!
那有一个 我看见了
There's one! I see it.
快去 快去
Go for it. Go for ii!
防御系统启动
Shield pressure plate activated.
快放烟雾 不 太早了
Throw the smoke! No, not yet.
Luke 你在等什么
Luke, what're you waiting for?
好的 准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
释放它
Pull it now!
现在释放烟雾
Smoke, now.
我来把车推回去
Let's get this car back in the race.
我操
Fuck!
耶 太爽了
Yeah! Great shit!
好的 宝贝 我们来了
Okay, baby, now we come.
武器系统启动
Sword plate activated.
去 去 快去开枪 快去开枪
Go, go! Get gun! Get gun!
小心后面 快闪开 Luke
Watch your back! Get your ass out of there, Luke.
一百万是我的啦 混蛋
Bounty is mine, motherfucker!
这家伙太讨厌了
I'm tired of this asshole.
是让他结束的时候了
Time to lose.
欧的神
Oh, my God.
抓紧
Hang on.
好好看看
Dig that!
还受得了吧
Still taking it, huh?
你死定了 来吧
You die! Come on!
今天我要让你死在这
Today! Today you die!
你会什么
What do you got, huh?
漂亮
Beautiful.
好的 直接去撞线吧
All right, ifs clear sailing to the finish line now.
你干什么
What are you doing?
那是我敌人的敌人 怎么回事
The enemy of my enemy. What's happening?
你完了
You die.
你能解释下你为什么我们拼死去救那个小子吗
You wanna tell me why you just risked our lives to save that banger?
他们是中国古惑仔 他们是Markus唯一不会雇佣的人
They're Triads. The only people Markus would not deal with.
这就是为什么他们不追杀我们 他们完全不知道怎么回事
That's why they're not after us. They have no clue about the hit.
这是一命换一命的交易
Look, it's a Triad kill thing. It's a life for a life.
我救了他的命 他就欠我一次
I save his, he owes me a favour.
好吧 那我也救了你 真的 怎么回事
Well, I saved your life. Really? How so?
因为你亲爱的Markus Kane用自由来诱惑我杀掉你
Because your Markus Kane offered to buy my freedom if I would kill you.
天啊他们都想干掉我 你也想吗
Jesus! They all want me dead, now you, too?
我想你也欠我一次了 我已经等不及还你了
I guess you owe me a favour, too. I can't wait.
我也想欠你的 滚开 Goldberg
Hey! I want a favour, too, huh? Fuck off, Goldberg.
好的 我抓到你了
Yeah, I got you, baby.
武器系统启动
Sword pressure plates activated.
前面有防具灯
Shield ahead.
防御系统启动
Shield pressure plate activated.
准备好了吗
Okay, ready?
用我旁边那个凝固汽油弹
Activate the napalm on my signal.
就现在
Now.
怎么回事 失灵了
What's this? It's not working!
出什么问题了
What's wrong?
这个东西坏了 中计了
This is not good, Luke. It's a setup.
耶 我来了 宝贝
Yeah. I'm coming, baby!
Goldberg 有人在我车上做了手脚
Hey, Goldberg. Someone had a play date with this car.
我现在什么东西都没有 没有枪 没有烟雾 什么都没有
I got nothing. No guns, no smoke, nothing.
来吧 让我撞死你个小娘们
Come on, hit it, you dumbass bitch!
转弯 转弯
Swerve! Swerve!
混蛋 快转弯
You, motherfucker! Tum!
我该怎么办
What can I do?
你用弹射座椅吧 不 你想要干什么
Brace yourself. No! What are you doing?
快想办法
Get the fuck out cf there!
快 你必须要想个办法
Come on! You need to gel out of there!
这是我的比赛
This is my tight.
你没得选抓紧
No choice. Hang on.
我来了
Here I come!
这个B一直打个不停
Motherfucker won't stop tiring!
红外线导弹就位
Heat seeking missile has been activated.
快点 快躲开
Come on! Hey! Get out of there!
来吧
Come on.
耶 我操 耶
Yeah! Shit! Yeah!
他妈的怎么了 你毁了你的后勤小组
What the fuck? You just killed your own pit crew.
婊子 闭上你的臭嘴
Bitch, you shut the fuck up.
嘿 快离开那
Goldberg. Hey, get out of there!
往车里拍 我想要一个特写
Get in that car! I want a close up.
快救我
Get me out of here!
天啊
Oh, God!
不
No!
我的天 不
Oh, my God, no!
来人啊
Somebody help!
Goldberg 快救他出来 快救他出来
Goldberg, get him out! Get him out!
不
No.
安息吧 Luke
Rest in peace, Luke.
你要为Luke的死负责 你他妈的在说什么
You gotta answer for Luke. What the fuck you talking about?
Katrina 说车子里面动了手脚
Katrina said ii was rigged from the inside.
而你他妈是唯一一个可以进到车里的人
And you're the only motherfucker that could have got to it.
是你杀了他吗
You killed him?
离我远点 你们两个混蛋
Getaway from me. Fuck you both.
我要跟他谈谈 不行
I need to talk to him. No.
他救了你的命
He saved your life!
你欠他的
You owe him.
一命换一命
A life for a life.
我知道该做什么
I know what to do.
他还在昏迷中 但幸运的是他的脉搏已经稳定了
We've induced coma. Thankfully all his vitals have stabilised
但是他需要得到更好的治疗
but he should be moved to a facility more suited to his needs.
这不是问题
Out of the question.
医生 外面有人想杀掉他
Doctor someone from the outside tried to kill him.
除非他们认为他死了才能回去交差
Unless they think he's dead, they'll come back to finish the job.
好吧 但我不能让他"被死亡"
Yeah, well, I can't pronounce a man dead while he's still alive.
你不能吗
Can't you?
我们怎么样才能找个人来代替Parks
How are we doing with finding a replacement for Parks?
她是从哈里伯顿（财富五百强）那边介绍过来的
She comes highly recommended from Halliburton.
她有顶级的拘留所
She ran their maximum security detention centre.
她很强很聪明 而且精力无限
She's strong. She's smart. Ruthlessly ambitious.
我想如果没有我不在场的话 她会跟人们说死亡赛车是她的点子
I think if I weren't around, she'd tell people that Death Race was her idea
而且她也肯定能说服人们
and she'd convince them that it was.
网络上的交接做好了吗
How's the switchover to the Internet?
已经做好了
Transitions complete.
那我们明天就开始全球直播
We start streaming live worldwide tomorrow.
我们赚的已经超过了付费电视
The numbers have already surpassed pay per view,
这得感谢Frankenstein的广告
thanks to the Frankenstein commercial.
等等 等等
Hold on. Wait.
我在想你所说的frankenstein
I've been meaning to talk to you about this Frankenstein.
你给他化妆了吗
Did you make him up?
Frankenstein是存在的
Frankenstein most certainly exists,
而且他明天将会出现在赛场上
and he will be in the race tomorrow.
那样最好
He better be.
他最好和广告上说的一样
And he better come as good as advertised.
手术的过程很惊险
The procedure's experimental and dangerous.
我们讨论过把电极插入了他的大脑
We're talking about placing electrodes into the brain.
你跟我他是最好的人选
You told me he was a perfect candidate.
噢 他当然是
Oh, he is.
但是我不敢保证
But there are no guarantees.
弄醒他吧
Let's wake him up.
Lucas 先生
Mn Lucas.
你刚刚经历二级烧伤 你全身有85%的地方都烧掉了
You've got second degree burns over 85% of your body.
现在 你很幸运地活了先来
Now you're lucky that you suffered no significant injuries.
骨头和器官都完好如初...
Not a broken bone or damaged organ,
...考虑到你经历了如此严重的烧伤
which is remarkable considering the intensity of the fire.
那么 这是地狱咯
So, this is hell?
为什么
Why?
除了地狱 你还能在哪
Where else would you be?
你还记得我
You do remember me.
赢五场你就自由了
You win five races and you're free.
你疯你妈的了
You're out of your fucking mind.
再也没有Markus Kane了 激发你的本能吧
No more Markus Kane trying to track you down.
你就像是重生了
Like a second chance.
看看我
Look at me.
真的 你看看我
Really. Look at me.
我这算是什么重生
What kind of second chance would I have?
不当Frankenstein的话 你就什么都不是了
You're either Frankenstein or you're nobody.
你不能再成为Carl Lucas了
You're certainly not Carl Lucas any more.
全世界都见证了他的火化
The entire world watched him incinerate.
那就是你的死亡证明
There's even a death certificate.
我可怜你
I pity you.
好吧 就算你不为自己想想
Okay If you don't do it for your life,
也要为Katrina想想
then you do it for Katrina.
我会让五个猥琐男去跟Katrina约会
I'll furlough five of my worst sodomites for a play date with sweet Katrina.
你想想她到时候还能活吗
By the time they're finished with hen she'll be lucky if she has a pulse.
感觉怎么样 Lucas先生
How do you feel, Mr. Lucas?
我的名字是
The name
不好意思让你失望了
Sorry 10 disappoint you.
你要和我这个墨西哥犹太人呆在一起了
You're gonna have to settle for the Mexican Jew,
三 二 一 开始
Three, two, one, and were in.
各位观众 晚上好 欢迎收看 死亡赛车
Good evening, and welcome to Death Race.
我们为来自全球的两千万观众直播这场赛事 而这周...
We're streaming live worldwide for over 20 million viewers. This week...
信号灯变绿的时候 马上切换到赛车手的宣传片
Cut in promos of the drivers as soon as the light hits green,
然后切回到我 抬起镜头 再一直跟着Frankenstein 明白了吗
cut back to me, crane up, chase out after Frankenstein, Got it?
恩 这看起来不错
Yeah. It'll look good.
是的 我知道这很不错
Yeah, I know it's a great shot.
是的 倒数五个数
it will be. Wen live in five.
好的 再来一次
Okay, time for one more.
镜头拉远
Go.
拉远
Go!
Lists在哪
Where's Lists?
他说他有点事情要处理
Said he had some business to take care of.
上车
Climb aboard.
怎么
What?
你本来以为是哥帅哥吗
You expecting another pretty boy?
观众朋友们 晚上好 欢迎收看 死亡赛车
Good evening, and welcome to Death Race.
我们正在为全球两千万观众直播
We're streaming live to over 20 million viewers.
这周 14k试图再次夺冠
This week, 14K attempts to repeat as champion.
但是他将遭到新的参赛者们的阻击
But he'll have fierce competition from several new drivers,
其中就包括 Frankenstein
including Frankenstein.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
谁拍你来的
Tell me who sent you.
祝你好运 Luke
Good for you, Luke.
这是你欠Lucas 的
Payback for Lucas.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God!
太棒了 这轮酒我请
Yes! The drinks are on me!
太棒了
Yes!
把我的打球的时间移到十点
Move my tee off time from 9:00 to 10:00.
你看见吗
You see that?
那就是个蠢娘们
Thats a stupid bitch.
你完事了
Take care of your business?
可惜Luke看不到了
I'm only sorry Luke didn't live to see this.
我不这么认为
I'm not so sure he didn't.
Frankenstein 是吗
Frankenstein, huh?
你有真名吗
You got a real name?
恩
Uh huh.
恩 当然 我有
Yeah, of course, I do.
来自Terminal岛的直播 最暴力 最惊悚
Live from Terminal Island televisions most violent most disturbing,
也是人类历史上收视率最高的节目
and most watched progmmme in human history.
关好灯 好戏即将上演
Dim the lights. The carnage is about to begin.
欢迎参加死亡赛车
Welcome to Death Race.
死亡赛车及其商标属于Weyland国际
Death Race is a trademark of Wayland International.